<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Digital Sketch Notes</title><link>https://cherrie.ink/</link><description>Recent content on Digital Sketch Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cherrie.ink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> A Smattering of Sources</title><link>https://cherrie.ink/posts/2023-08-03-smattering-of-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cherrie.ink/posts/2023-08-03-smattering-of-sources/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s crazy that the internet enables me to open up a browser and find art from amazing artists of exactly the subject that I&amp;rsquo;m trying to study.
That&amp;rsquo;s insane! Style is so interesting, I love to sit here and synthesize.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brother Bear</title><link>https://cherrie.ink/posts/2023-08-02-brother-bear/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cherrie.ink/posts/2023-08-02-brother-bear/</guid><description>&lt;p>Some studies from Brother Bear and also John Nevarez. Stylistically, Brother Bear leans pretty heavily into realism.
Thus I can understand why audience reception of the film noted that the animation was &amp;ldquo;weak&amp;rdquo;— it doesn&amp;rsquo;t push the medium and feel snappy in the way that great animation &lt;em>can&lt;/em> feel. It is, however, nice to take a look at how they drew bears 2D.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bear Studies</title><link>https://cherrie.ink/posts/2023-08-01-bear-study/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cherrie.ink/posts/2023-08-01-bear-study/</guid><description>&lt;p>Periodically, I identify areas or subjects of drawing that I&amp;rsquo;d like to improve at. Most recently, it&amp;rsquo;s bears. The resulting action is usually me taking a few days to sit with it and grind through a lot of drawings—though most of this never sees the light of day.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>The thing about this practice though, is that it&amp;rsquo;s usually relegated to some throwaway sketchbook that I promptly forget about&amp;hellip;whereas I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought it would be more valuable if I could collect the learnings so I could revisit them to get a refresher. Below are the few from yesterday (July 31, 2023):&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cherrie Dot Ink!</title><link>https://cherrie.ink/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cherrie.ink/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s not written with physical ink but here it is nonetheless! A digital diary to collect my musings and current happenings.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It has been a very long time since I&amp;rsquo;ve opened up a file and fiddled with html and css— but thanks to some helpful pointers from other smart people on the internet, BEHOLD. A blog up and running that is working just fine.
We&amp;rsquo;re past the halfway point of 2023, so not really the time for New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions but&amp;hellip; as I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a little hiatus and enjoying some summer holiday time, I found the energy to finally put together a space for my thoughts on the internet. So now we have a half-year resolution to write weekly at the very least.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>